<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="52"><page Index="1" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ ]]></page><page Index="2" isMAC="false"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="3" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[    ]]></page><page Index="4" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                  Contents
4 Organization and Responsibilities
6 Promotion of National
Science & Technology Development National Science & Technology Development Policies
National Science & Technology Development Plan Government-funded Science & Technology Development Programs National Science & Technology Literacy and Competence Nationwide Research & Development Status and Trends
12
28
   Support for Academic Research
Research Grants Research Highlights
Core Facilities and Precious Instruments Science & Technology Talents
Science & Technology Exchange and Cooperation
 Enhancement of Academia-Industry
Relationship and Innovation
Academia-Industry-Research Collaboration Innovation and Entrepreneurship
      ]]></page><page Index="5" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                                             32
36 42
48
Incubation of Startups
From Intellectual Property to Initial Public Offering
Green Energy Technology Joint Research & Development Program Artificial Intelligence Innovation Ecosystem
 Development of Science Parks
Features & Locations Status of Development Smart Science Parks
Foundations and
Administrative Institution
National Applied Research Laboratories
National Synchrotron Radiation Research Center
National Science & Technology Center for Disaster Reduction
  Publications Directory
      ]]></page><page Index="6" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
PromoVtisioion ofofr N20a3t0ional
Make Taiwan Innovative, Inclusive and Sustainable
Science & Technology Development
Six priority areas for development in the next decade:
National Science & Technology Development Policies
To realize the vision, MOST strengthens cooperation with other ministries to understand the needs of diverse populations, integrate innovative technologies into various aspects of everyday life, and create opportunities for new sustainable industries.
The Ministry of Science and Technology (MOST), originally established as the National Science Council (NSC), Executive Yuan on February 1, 1959, is the govern-
Formulating national S&T development policy
Coordinating and evaluating S&T development projects
technological development. Its three main missions are promoting nationwide S&T development, supporting academic research, and developing science parks.
Managing National S&T Development Fund, Executive Yuan
MOST 's Responsibilities
In this age of knowledge economy, S&T
innovation has become the key driver of
economic growth and national progress. As
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice
such, the NSC was reorganized and
in science parks. Application such as environmental monitoring and information network, intelligent transportation
became MOST on March 3, 2014 with a new
Overseeing Promoting
system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipment management, monitoring and integration system,
organizational structure aiming to strength- issues related R&D policies in
intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in
en the integration of academic research with
development
frontier industrial
conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster
industrial development. On one hand,
science parks
energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficient transportation and traffic safety, thus creating a
MOST continues the traditions of promoting
convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest-
academia-industry partnership and encour-
ment.
aging innovations; on the other hand, it
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera-
reinforces the impetus for R&D in industry,
tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on public roofs and set up demonstration sites of
fosters S&T creativity, assists startups and
distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy-
support industrial development.
cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for
In face of ever-changing international circumstances, domestic problems arisen from the aging society,
environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental quality. Such information would be included in the smart park database to be processed using big data analytics
challenges posed by life-changing new technologies, MOST formulates future national S&T policies with
for intelligence science park environmental management.
socio-economic, environmental and political considerations.
other
and evaluating
to S&T
Developing
technology
Precision Health Semiconductors Digital Transformation
AI and 6G Wireless Network Information Security Forward-looking Network Infrastructure
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Organization and Responsibilities
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
Smart Science Parks projects and
research Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019academic
Promoting basic and applied S&T research
Supporting major S&T R&D
]]></page><page Index="7" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Organization Chart
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
Promotion of National
Department of Planning
ServingasthecoreforTaiwan'sbiomedicalDsecpieanrtcmeernetsoefaNracthuranl dindustrydevelopment,theHsinchuBiomedi- Sciences and Sustainable
Science & Technology Development
cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical
Development
Science and Product R&D Center, the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu
Department of Engineering
Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all
National Science & Technology Development Policies
and Technologies
under one umbrella. With focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides clinical trials, business seed planning, an innovative R&D network (R&D facilities and talent), clinical trial coopera-
Department of Life Sciences
tion, and regulatory consulting services. Among the 58 approved companies in the Park, 24 specializes in R&D of
new pharmaceuticals
Hsinchu Science Park Bureau
Science and Technology
Advisory Board
Department of Humanities and Social Sciences
Minister
Deputy Minister Deputy Minister Vice Minister
Department of Foresight and Innovation Policies
Chief Secretary
Department of General Affairs
National Science and Technology Center for Disaster Reduction
Department of International Cooperation and Science Education
Central Taiwan Science Park Bureau
Department of Academia- Industry Collaboration and Science Park Affairs
Southern Taiwan Science Park Bureau
Department of Personnel
Department of Government Ethics
National Applied Research Laboratories
Department of Budget, Accounting and Statistics
National Synchrotron Radiation Research Center
Department of Information Services
Legal Affairs Committee
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
Number of Employees
2,551
276 MOST headquarters (as of July 2020)
467 Subordinate agencies
1,808 Foundations and administrative institution
(under MOST supervision)
"
]]></page><page Index="8" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
Promotion of National Science & Technology Development
National Science & Technology Development Policies
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice in science parks. Application such as environmental monitoring and information network, intelligent transportation system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipment management, monitoring and integration system, intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficient transportation and traffic safety, thus creating a convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest- ment.
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera- tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on public roofs and set up demonstration sites of distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy- cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental quality. Such information would be included in the smart park database to be processed using big data analytics for intelligence science park environmental management.
Smart Science Parks
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
]]></page><page Index="9" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
Promotion of National
Serving as the core for Taiwan's biomedical science research and industry development, the Hsinchu Biomedi-
Science & Technology Development
Jointly implemented by 17 ministries/departments/agencies, Academia Sinica, Board of Science cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical
and Technology, Department of Cyber Security, National Development Fund, and local govern- Science and Product R&D Center, the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu
ments, the National Science and Technology Development Plan (2017-2020) contains four goals: Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all
National Science & Technology Development Policies
under one umbrella. With focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides clinical trials, business seed planning, an innovative R&D network (R&D facilities and talent), clinical trial coopera- tion, and regulatory consulting services. Among the 58 approved companies in the Park, 24 specializes in R&D of new pharmaceuticals
Revive economic dynamics through innovation
Cultivate and recruit talents with diverse career paths
Develop robust smart living technologies and industries
Enhance innovation ecosystem for scientific research
budget as well as planning, coordinating, and assessing S&T development programs conducted by central government departments/agencies. In the early stages of these programs, MOST reviews key implementation points, funding, and obtained results; strengthens integration and connection among related programs; and establishes a complete database of all assessment information.
National Science & Technology Development Plan
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
Government-funded Science & Technology Development Programs
]]></page><page Index="10" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                                                                                                                                                                                                                                Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
National Science & Technology Literacy and Competence
 MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
Landmark Taipei 101 lit up for IYPT-150
Landmark Taipei 101 lit up for IYPT-150
  Smart Science Parks
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
Decorated metro compartment in celebration of IYPT-150
8
   Promotion of National Science & Technology Development
To enhance national S&T literacy and competence, MOST actively promotes popular science communica-
National Science & Technology Development Policies
tion through publishing the popular science magazine Science Development and reporting on a wide range of scientific knowledge. MOST also funds academia-in- dustry collaboration on the production of media content including films, videos, picture books, and animations on popular science.
Annual funding has been provided to support diverse science popularization activities including public talks and exhibitions to promote basic science knowledge and popular science education to the general public, in remote areas and among the aborigines. The “Sci-Tech
serves as an online platform for sharing popular science resources, while communication apps and social networking services such as LINE, YouTube, Instagram and Plurk strengthen science-related interaction with and among the general public.
Innovative activities have been organized to foster integration of scientific knowledge with everyday life and to bridge the gap between science and society.
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice in science parks. Application such as environmental monitoring and information network, intelligent transportation system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipment management, monitoring and integration system, intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficient transportation and traffic safety, thus creating a convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest- ment.
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera- tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on public roofs and set up demonstration sites of distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy- cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental quality. Such information would be included in the smart park database to be processed using big data analytics for intelligence science park environmental management.
]]></page><page Index="11" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
Promotion of National
Serving as the core for Taiwan's biomedical science research and industry development, the Hsinchu Biomedi-
To inspire scientific exploration:
Science & Technology Development
cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical
The Taiwan Railways of Popular Science train
Science and Product R&D Center, the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu
Empower remote areas and offshore islands with scientific knowledge through
Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all
National Science & Technology Development Policies
exhibitions and activities jointly organized by academic institutions and
under one umbrella. With focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides
clinical trials, businersespsecetdivpelacnitnyinagn,dacnoiunntoyvgaotivernRm&eDnntsetwork (R&D facilities and talent), clinical trial coopera- tion, and regulatory consulting services. Among the 58 approved companies in the Park, 24 specializes in R&D of new pharmaceuticals
To enhance scientific intellect:
Exhibitions, seminars and special reports with
specific themes of “today in the history of science”
Activities in commemoration of landmark scientific discoveries:
- International Year (150th Anniversary) of the Periodic Table (IYPT), 2019 - 60th Anniversary of the Invention of Laser, 2020
“Kiss Science” with large-scale Open House activities in island-wide research institutions for young students to gain a close-up perspective of science and popular science knowledge
of diverse disciplines
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
To promote scientific exchange:
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
Dance performance at opening ceremony of Kiss Science
 
]]></page><page Index="12" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Nationwide Research & Development Status and Trends
Promotion of National Science & Technology Development
National Science & Technology Development Policies
As a percentage of GDP (%)
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice in science parks. Application such as environmental monitoring and information network, intelligent transportation system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipment management, monitoring and integration system, intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficient transportation and traffic safety, thus creating a convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest- ment.
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera- tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on public roofs and set up demonstration sites of distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy- cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental quality. Such information would be included in the smart park database to be processed using big data analytics for intelligence scienceNoptea:rOktherndvoimroesntimc secntotraslinmcluadne ahighemr edeuncat.tion sector and private non-profit
sector. Some percentages may not total 100% due to rounding effects.
Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
A nationwide survey has been annually conducted since 1981 to gain an overall picture of R&D status and trends in government, higher education, private business and non-profit sectors. Information on research input indicators including gross domestic expenditures on R&D and human resources engaged in R&D, as well as data on research output indicators including research papers published, patents grant- ed, and technology balance of payments are compiled and published in Indicators of Science and Tech- nology, Taiwan.
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies,
Gross Domestic Expenditure on R&D, 2014-2018
MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government
depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Unit: US$ 1 million
20,000 15,000 10,000
5,000 0
4%
3%
2%
1% 0%
16,151
17,054
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
2014 2015 2.98% 3%
2016 2017 2018
2014 2015
Smart Science Parks
18,059
19,150
20,532
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
2014
2015
2016
2017
2018
0.2 0.9
21.9 77.0
0.2 0.9
21.2 77.7
0.2 0.8
21.4 77.6
0.2 0.8
19.8 79.2
0.1 0.8
18.8 80.3
3.09% 3.19%
3.36%
2016 2017 2018
R&D Expenditure by Source of Funds (%), 2014-2018
]]></page><page Index="13" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
Promotion of National
Serving as the core for Taiwan's biomedical science research and industry development, the Hsinchu Biomedi- cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical
Science & Technology Development
Science and Product R&D Center, the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all
National Science & Technology Development Policies
under one umbrella. With focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides clinical trials, business seed planning, an innovative R&D network (R&D facilities and talent), clinical trial coopera- tion, and regulatory consulting services. Among the 58 approved companies in the Park, 24 specializes in R&D of new pharmaceuticals
Source: (1) SCI: InCites, Clarivate Analytics (Updated: January 2020)
()
239,974
245,401
250,495
Human Resources in R&D, 2014-2018
255,229
262,307
142,458 144,836 147,141
149,886 153,998
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T develo2p9m,97e9nt. To ens30u,7re23 integrated31,a39n1d consiste3n2t,23i7mplementat3io3,n087of development policies,
21.0 21.3 21.3 21.5
MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government
12.9 12.9 13.1
depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Note: Figures are based on full-time equivalents.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Numbers of Papers Published and U.S. Utility Patents Granted, 2014 -2018
28,117/18
12,271/5
3,860 /16 3,865 /17 2014 2015
27,035/21
27,101/21
25,917/12
25,710/22
11,424/6
4,244 /21 2018
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
Numbers of Papers and Citations in SCI, 2010-2018
12,317/5
4,327/17 2016
12,738/5
4,056 /20 2017
12,540/6
828,013/19
136,859/21
2011 - 2015
Source: InCites, Clarivate Analytics (Updated: January 2020)
850,483/21
133,880/21
2014 - 2018
7279,66/19
13,794/17
792,033/19
13,974/17
823,120/19
139,048/19
2010 - 2014
2012 - 2016
2013 - 2017
21.5 13.2 13.5
]]></page><page Index="14" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
Promotion of National Science & Technology Development
National Science & Technology Development Policies
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice in science parks. Application such as environmental monitoring and information network, intelligent transportation system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipment management, monitoring and integration system, intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficient transportation and traffic safety, thus creating a convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest- ment.
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera- tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on public roofs and set up demonstration sites of distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy- cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental quality. Such information would be included in the smart park database to be processed using big data analytics for intelligence science park environmental management.
Support for Academic Research
Research Grants
To promote S&T development, MOST supports academic research through providing grants
to educational and research institutions. Research projects approved after two stringent rounds
of review can receive funding from MOST for research personnel, equipment and facilities,
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national
books and references, consumable materials, and overseas travel expenses.
S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies,
In 2019, MOST
had allocated researchS&grTandtsevteolo1p7m3epnut bpliclanasndpproripvoastedunbiyvedrsififteieresnat ngdovernment MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates
depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
colleges and 134 research institutes.
Grant Allocation by Discipline, 2019
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
Smart Science Parks
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
Number of Research Projects Funded, 2015-2019
Note: The majority of projects are implemented from August 1 to July 31 of the following year
]]></page><page Index="15" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
Promotion of National
Serving as the core for Taiwan's biomedical science research and industry development, the Hsinchu Biomedi- cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical
Science & Technology Development
Science and Product R&D Center, the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu To strengthen R&D in areas of national
Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all National Science & Technology sDtreengvtheolr okepy tmechenonlotgiePs, oprloimcotieinsno- under one umbrella. With focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides vation, and nurture outstanding young lead-
clinical trials, business seed planning, an innovative R&D network (R&D facilities and talent), clinical trial coopera- ers, MOST screens and selects the cream tion, and regulatory consulting services. Among the 58 approved companies in the Park, 24 specializes in R&D of among research centers with grants from the
new pharmaceuticals
Ministry of Education (MOE). Upon review, extra funding will be offered to centers exploring key studies on special disciplines that seek to resolve major scientific, social, or industrial issues of the nation. It is hoped that these additional financial resources will
advantage and international standing in S&T, achieve breakthroughs in key industries, and improve well-being of the people.
Academic Summit Program
Established in 2009, the Academic
Summit Program promotes forward-looking
basic and applied research by providing
ample long-term funding to world-leading
research teams and outstanding scholars
with high research potential. The program
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward
the vision and strategies for national
S&T devealoimpmsentto. Tcoultievnasteureinitnetrengartaiotendallyandisctionn-sistent implementation of development policies,
MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government guished researchers in various disciplines.
depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
Additional funding for research centers exploring key studies on special disciplines
]]></page><page Index="16" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
Seeing the Unseeable - First Image of Black Hole Captured
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
Promotion of National
Research Highlights
Science & Technology Development
Natural Sciences
National Science & Technology Development Policies
First image of a black hole in the heart of the massive distant galaxy Messier87, residing 55 million light-years from Earth with a mass 6.5-billion times that of the Sun
Unveil the first direct visual evidence of a supermassive black hole and its shadow, confirming
Taiwan has been a member of the Event Horizon Telescope Collaboration, an international project with a planet scale array of 8 ground-based radio telescopes
Significant contribution made possible through the Greenland Telescope, linked with the Submillimeter Array and the James Clerk Maxwell Telescope in Hawaii, and the Atacama Large Millimeter/Submillimeter Array in Chile.
A pioneering find in the study of black hole astrophysics, opening new window on the study of gravitation and astronomy
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice in science parks. Application such as environmental monitoring and information network, intelligent transportation system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipment management, monitoring and integration system, intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficient transportation and traffic safety, thus creating a convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest- ment.
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera- tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on public roofs and set up demonstration sites of distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy- cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental quality. Such information would be included in the smart park database to be processed using big data analytics for intelligence science park environmental management.
Smart Science Parks
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
Atacama Large Millimeter/submillimeter Array (ALMA) in northern Chile
Atacama Large Millimeter/submillimeter Array (ALMA) in northern Chile
]]></page><page Index="17" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
Promotion of National
Serving as the core for Taiwan's biomedical science research and industry development, the Hsinchu Biomedi- cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical
Science & Technology Development
Science and Product R&D Center, the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu
Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all
National Science & Technology Development Policies
under one umbrella. With focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides clinical trials, business seed planning, an innovative R&D network (R&D facilities and talent), clinical trial coopera- tion, and regulatory consulting services. Among the 58 approved companies in the Park, 24 specializes in R&D of new pharmaceuticals
New logarithm developed for probing deformation using 14-year postseismic GPS satellite data Reveal non-linear relationship between stress and strain rate beneath the Taiwan orogenic belt Energy budget of mountain building reduced by short-term modulation of lower-crustal strength Geodetic observations with potential for accessing rock rheological properties under natural settings across different spatial and temporal scales
Contribute to disaster risk assessment and earthquake prevention
Breakthrough in Technical Bottleneck of Magnetic Random Access Memory (MRAM)
- non-volatile memory depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
MRAM, a rising star with potential to become universal memory and growing market demand by AI and IoT devices
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrateAdvantdagceosnosfisMteRnAt Mim: plementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government
- no data loss even when power is removed - no data degradation over time
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
- no booting required
- high operation speed; low power consumption
layers separated by a thin insulating layer
Free top ferromagnetic layer for rapid information processing Pinned bottom ferromagnetic layer for stable information storage
Promising approach for switching ferromagnetic magnetization of next-generation MRAM
Geodetic Observations Shed Light on Spatio-temporal Evolution of Crustal Rheology
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
GPS station at Nantou County
]]></page><page Index="18" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
Fight against Global Warming – New Single-atom Iron Catalyst
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
Mission impossible - Watching Typhoons from Within the Storm
State-of-the-art single-atom iron catalyst for CO2 reduction
Scientific breakthrough in line with international trends of green energy and has great commercial value in future development
Promotion of National
Science & Technology Development
Buoys for real-time measurements of oceanic and atmospheric responses to passing typhoons High-resolution meteorological and subsea data advance our knowledge of air-sea exchanges and reveal properties and dynamics of typhoons
Large-scale electrochemical reduction of CO2 to CO made
possible with a new low-cost catalyst
Potential substitute for catalysts made with gold, silver or
National Science & Technology Development Policies
other precious metals
Single-atom dispersed iron ions in +3 oxidation state can achieve CO2
extremely low voltage
energy consumption contributes to a perfect carbon cycle Electrochemical CO2 reduction ameliorates global warming for human welfare
Conversion of CO2 into chemical fuels generates alternative
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice Cross-disciplinary research findings translated into
in science parks. Application such as environmental monitoring and information network, intelligent transportation computer programs, representing a major milestone
system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipment management, monitoring and integration system,
in precise and timely prediction of typhoons
intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in
Data are shared as part of the TOMATO (TOwards
conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster
Multiple Arrays for Typhoon Observations) frame-
energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficient transportation and traffic safety, thus creating a
cwoonrvkenthieanttdliveipnlgoysspawceathnedranbuidoeyasl eantdreupnredneerwuraiatelrenvironment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest- ment.
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera- In-situ information relayed to Central Weather
tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on public roofs and set up demonstration sites of Bureau for timely warnings to be issued for typhoon
distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy- disaster mitigation
cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for Meteorological buoys serving as sentinels for protec-
environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental
tion of life and protection Buoys deployed for real-time typhoon data
quality. Such information would be included in the smart park database to be processed using big data analytics
for intelligence science park environmental management.
Smart Science Parks
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
]]></page><page Index="19" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
Promotion of National
Serving as the core for Taiwan's biomedical science research and industry development, the Hsinchu Biomedi-
Science & Technology Development
cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical
World-leading innovative technology developed under cross-disciplinary collaboration
Science and Product R&D Center, the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu
High-efficiency capacitive deionization (CDI) achieved using electrode made with novel nitrogen-doped Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all
National Science & Technology Development Policies
undernaonoepuomroburseclla.rbWonith focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides
clinicaZletorilaitlisc,ibmuisdianzeoslsatseeferdampleawnnoirnkg(,ZaIFn-i8n)ncoovmatpivoesRite&-Ddenrievtewdocrkar(bRo&nDefxahciibliittiiensgalanrdgtealseunrtf)a,celinaicreaal tarinadl choiogphera-
tion, and regulatory consulting services. Among the 58 approved companies in the Park, 24 specializes in R&D of micropore volume contributes to increase electrosorption capacity
new pharmaceuticals
Electrical conductivity further enhanced by adding gold nanoparticles or poly(3,4-ethylenedioxy-
thio-phene) (PEDOT) into the ZIF-8 framework
Achieved electrosorption capacity three times higher than commercially available activated carbon High-performance CDI under low-voltage operation has potential applications in water reuse and desali-
nation, hard water softening, and wastewater treatment
Engineering Sciences
Nanoporous Carbon Material for High-performance Capacitive Deionization
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
Layered structure of CDI system
]]></page><page Index="20" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                                                                                                                                                                                                               18
Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
Healthier and Safer Society with Smart Face and Emotion Recognition Technology
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
 Smart Science Parks
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
Vital biosignals monitored automatically by camera in living room
   Promotion of National Science & Technology Development
Smart healthcare facilitated by vision-based biosignal health management system with vital physiological signals measured and detected through visuals without contact
National Science & Technology Development Policies
Motion and illumination robust, overcoming inaccurate detection by wearable devices under vigorous movements or poor lighting conditions
Facial information obtained through a camera and analyzed by intelligent algorithm yields blood pressure, heart rate, heat rate variability measurements
High-precision AI system integrated with deep learning and physiological information measure- ment with easy application
                                                                                         remote face detection with accuracy and fast calculation
Real-time high-speed face recognition has applications in medical and healthcare sectors for contactless round-the-clock biosignal monitoring
                                                                                                the detected not feeling the existence of the device
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice in science parks. Application such as environmental monitoring and information network, intelligent transportation system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipment management, monitoring and integration system, intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficient transportation and traffic safety, thus creating a convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest- ment.
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera- tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on public roofs and set up demonstration sites of distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy- cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental quality. Such information would be included in the smart park database to be processed using big data analytics for intelligence science park environmental management.
]]></page><page Index="21" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
Promotion of National
Serving as the core for Taiwan's biomedical science research and industry development, the Hsinchu Biomedi- cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical
Science & Technology Development
Science and Product R&D Center, the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu
- expedite the exploration of new drugs and novel materials
Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all
National Science & Technology Development Policies
-                                                                                       
under one umbrella. With focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides
clinical tria-lsf,abcuilistaintescsosnesetrducptliaonnoinfgu,nacnonindnitoiovnaatilvlyesRe&cDureneintwforrmka(Rtio&nDafnadcicliotiemsmaunndictalteionnt)s, ycslinteicmasl trial coopera-
tion, and r-egbuelcaotomryectohneskueltyintgo sresrveiacrecsh. Aremquoinrigngthlear5g8e-aspcparloevaenddccoomppalneixescoinmtphuetaPtaiornk,s24 specializes in R&D of
new pharmaceuticals
- enable technology to manage and process huge amounts of information with great security -                                                                   
                                                                            
Lead the world in experimental demonstration of revival of two-photon interference
Show feasibility of performing high purity, long-distance quantum interference in future applica- tion of quantum chips
Established leading-edge technologies related to on-chip quantum optical computing
Aim to realize multiplexing silicon photonic quantum chips with the ability to perform fault-toler- ant quantum computation at room temperature
Scalable Quantum Photonic Computing Chip
 !                                                                                          !
!
!
!
!
!
!
!
!MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national !
S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies,
!
MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government de!part-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
!
Schematic of scalable quantum photonic computing chip
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
  
]]></page><page Index="22" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Life Sciences
Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
Promotion of National Science & Technology Development
National Science & Technology Development Policies
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice in science parks. Application such as environmental monitoring and information network, intelligent transportation system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipment management, monitoring and integration system, intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficient transportation and traffic safety, thus creating a convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest- ment.
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera-
tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on publiPcharolaoenfsopsaisnodrchsiedst: luarpged(Pe.mReodnBsetlrl)aatniodnsmsailtle(Ps. of
Gold Diamond), and their respective epidermal cells in distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy-
petals
cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for
environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental quality. Such information would be included in the smart park database to be processed using big data analytics for intelligence science park environmental management.
To Shake or Not To Shake – Understanding the Pathophysiology of Essential Tremor
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
Smart Science Parks
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
]]></page><page Index="23" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
Promotion of National
Serving as the core for Taiwan's biomedical science research and industry development, the Hsinchu Biomedi- cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical
Science & Technology Development
Science and Product R&D Center, the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu
Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all
National Science & Technology Development Policies
under one umbrella. With focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides clinical trials, business seed planning, an innovative R&D network (R&D facilities and talent), clinical trial coopera- tion, and regulatory consulting services. Among the 58 approved companies in the Park, 24 specializes in R&D of new pharmaceuticals
Biotechnical Advances in Functional Aquafeed Additives
Taiwan, known as “the grouper kingdom”, ranks second in annual global production value of grouper acquaculture Development of functional aquafeed additive in feed, using
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national as nutrition source
S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies,
Unsaturated fatty acid in algae changes serotonin and blood
MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government
depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Indoor Pond of Grouper Broodstock
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Substitute 20% of animal protein feed
Reduce feed production costs & increase harvesting rates
Novel Optical Microscopies to Unravel Mystery of Brain Function
Developed new optical micro-imaging platform to capture physiological dynamics of neurons in a living Drosophila brain, whose neural network connection is similar to human brain
First high-speed volumetric imaging system that provides millisecond temporal resolution
Achieved volumetric all-optical physiology observation to resolve 3D neural connection and coding of visual circuits in a Drosophila brain
Developed deep-tissue super-solution imaging (COOL, Confocal lOcalization deep-imaging with Optical cLear-
optical clearing, and localization microscopy to achieve 20-nm spatial resolution
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
Two tightly entangled neural fibers distinguished under deep-tissue super-solution imaging
Provided unprecedented depth/resolution performance to three-dimensionally resolve densely entangled dendritic
Paves the way toward whole-brain neural network studies Applicable to other high-resolution imaging in biological tissues
Target at observation of connections among every single neuron during learning and memory formation, with high temporal resolution (millisecond), high spatial resolution (sub-micrometer to nanometer), and high penetration depth (millimeter), to unravel the mysteries of brain function.
]]></page><page Index="24" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
Promotion of National Science & Technology Development
National Science & Technology Development Policies
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice in science parks. Application such as environmental monitoring and information network, intelligent transportation system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipment management, monitoring and integration system, intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficient transportation and traffic safety, thus creating a convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest- ment.
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera- tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on public roofs and set up demonstration sites of distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy- cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental quality. Such information would be included in the smart park database to be processed using big data analytics for intelligence science park environmental management.
Humanities and Social Sciences
Salvaging 5000 years of Human History
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
Smart Science Parks
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
]]></page><page Index="25" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
Promotion of National
Serving as the core for Taiwan's biomedical science research and industry development, the Hsinchu Biomedi- cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical
Science & Technology Development
Science and Product R&D Center, the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu
Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all
National Science & Technology Development Policies
under one umbrella. With focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides clinical trials, business seed planning, an innovative R&D network (R&D facilities and talent), clinical trial coopera- tion, and regulatory consulting services. Among the 58 approved companies in the Park, 24 specializes in R&D of new pharmaceuticals
Science education for indigenous people
Has covered 8 indigenous ethnic groups
Developed textbooks, teaching materials, picture books, e-books, and cloud learning platforms Organize annual “Indigenous Science Festival”
Science for Sports – Better Performance, Less Injury
Promote cross-disciplinary research in Precision Sport Science Aims - Understand needs of elite athletes
Assist solving bottlenecks in training to enhance performance
Focus - Sport science training,
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national Physical rehabilitation and injury prevention,
S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies,
MOST reviews,Temcohniitcoarsl aannddtaectvicaalulatneaslySsi&sT development plans proposed by different government
depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences. Sports - Baseball, Badminton, Table tennis, Weightlifting, and Cycling
Fruits of success
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
-Wireless foot pressure insoles
-Electronic strike Karma Zone
-Smart table tennis rackets
-Tactical analysis systems
-Badminton serving machines and smart rackets International cooperation or patent applications are in progress
Smart table tennis rackets &Tactical Analysis syetem
In the future, the sports industry will be linked, the research results will be industrialized, and the development of the industry will be promoted to create economic value
Return to Basics - Science Education for the Indigenes
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
- Cultivation of teachers
- Research and curriculum planning
- Development of teaching materials on the basis of knowledge system of indigenous people - Set up evaluation tools to test true ability of indigenous students
- Enhancement of reading ability
- Promotion of popular science activities
- to arouse interest in science and technology among the indigenous
- to foster understanding of indigenous wisdom of science among the public
]]></page><page Index="26" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
Core Facilities and Precious Instruments
Precious Instruments
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Biotech and pharmaceutical core facilities
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
Promotion of National Science & Technology Development
To ensure proper maintenance and effective use of precious instruments for research in various
National Science & Technology Development Policies
disciplines and to maximize the efficiency of resource sharing, MOST has since 1980 subsidized universi- ties to establish precious instrument centers and invited experts for supervision and consultation on use of instruments. Trained personnel have also been hired to operate the instruments and to perform analy- sis, providing domestic researchers with convenient testing services.
MOST began subsidizing biotechnology and pharmaceutical core facilities in 2011 to stimu- late innovation and R&D, build up clinical research capabilities, utilize and integrate S&T resources more effectively, and accelerate the development of industrial applications. The facilities offer high-level services and profes- sional consultation to meet the needs of
research communities, and their resources have been widely used to provide a major boost to
high-quality R&D environment, developing pioneering technologies, and building compre- hensive links to industries, this initiative will drive
To promote innovative transformation an-d to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice
in science parks. Application such as environmentalEmlecotnrointosrpinecgtroasncdopiynforrcmheamtioicnal naneatlwysoisrk, intelligent transportation maceutical industries.
system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipment management, monitoring and integration system,
intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in
conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster
energTyheanrdolewaotfebrrsaainvinagc,tivciatyrbionnthaendmwenatsatelfruendcuticotnioing,eoffichiuemntatnrasnhsapsorbtaetcionmaenadntriamffpicorstanfettyto,pthicusincreatinga
convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest- humanities and social sciences research — one that is receiving considerable attention in scientifically
ment.
advanced nations around the globe. To keep Taiwan apace with this trend, MOST is installing magnetic
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera- resonance imaging scanners and magnetoencephalography scanners at several leading universities as
tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on public roofs and set up demonstration sites of part of its plans to equip domestic researchers with the tools they need. Together, these universities form
distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy- the Brain Research Initiative Net for Mind Science and make the scanners available for shared use.
cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental quality. Such information would be included in the smart park database to be processed using big data analytics for intelligence science park environmental management.
Smart Science Parks
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
Brain and mind science core facilities
]]></page><page Index="27" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Science & Technology Talents
Cultivating Talents
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
Promotion of National
Serving as the core for Taiwan's biomedical science research and industry development, the Hsinchu Biomedi-
Science & Technology Development
To cultivate talents and to encourage pursuit of academic studies, MOST offers scholarships to 300 cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical
outstanding doctoral students, US$16,000 per year for four years. Universities with doctoral students Science and Product R&D Center, the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu
awarded the scholarships and with proposals made for the “Excellence lmprovement for Doctoral Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all
National Science & Technology Development Policies
Students Scheme” will be granted extra subsidy at a maximum of US$10 million per year for four years. under one umbrella. With focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides
To nurture doctoral students, courses and exchange acvtivities are planned for all-round self-enhance- clinical trials, business seed planning, an innovative R&D network (R&D facilities and talent), clinical trial coopera-
tion, and mreegnutlaintoreysceoanrscuhltlintegrasceyrv, itceeasm. -Abmuioldnigngthaeb5ili8tya, papnrdovinendocvoamtivpeasnpieirsit.in the Park, 24 specializes in R&D of
new pharmaceuticals
To broaden global perspectives, subsidies are provided for graduate students to attend international
conferences or for Ph.D. students and post-doctoral fellows to gain overseas research exposure.
Ongoing measures for recruiting S&T talents include engaging visiting academics and postdoctoral researchers in local projects, inviting research scholars to carry out medium- and long-term studies, and the Leaders in Future Trends (LIFT) program to entice overseas science and technology elites back to Taiwan. Professional exchanges and sharing of expertise and experiences by the returned talents would contribute to enrich and enhance domestic industries.
academic honor to recognize innovative researchers who have made monumental contributions to Taiwan society. The award is conferred every two years, and MOST organizes the nomination and selec- tion process. The Executive Yuan commends exceptional S&T talents in Taiwan through the Executive Yuan Outstanding Contribution in Science and Technology Award.
MOST honors distinguished talents who have conducted basic research, research that significantly improve human lives, knowledge and technology with the Outstanding Research Award. MOST also confers the Ta-You Wu Memorial Award annually to cultivate young researchers for long-term academic research careers.
Recruitment of S&T Talents, 2015-2019
Recruiting Talents
Funding Unit: US$1 million Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
70,7
2,660
Person-times
2019
64,8
2,488
2015
64,5
2,471
58,0
2,138
58,9
2,203
2016
2017
2018
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
Awarding Talents
]]></page><page Index="28" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                                                                                                                                 Science &Technology Exchange and Cooperation
Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
 Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
International S&T Cooperation
Smart Science Parks
International Exchange of S&T Personnel
Cross-strait S&T Exchange
MOST fosters S&T personnel exchange and cooperation between China and Taiwan through joint research on issues of common interest; recruiting S&T personnel from China; encouraging and supporting cross-strait S&T seminars; inviting scientists from China, Hong Kong and Macau for short-term visits; and approving visits of mainland academics and scientists for short- and long-term exchange.
    To promote bilateral and mul-tilateral S&T exchange with other coun-
tries, MOST has signed 119 cooperation agreements with 43 nations,
the European Union, the European Organization for Nuclear Research, and the European Molecular Biology
Conference and European Molecular Biology Organization. Cooperation takes the form of building exchanges
among researchers, organizing joint symposia, conducting collaborative research projects, promoting high-level
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice
official visits, and conferring international awards such as the Prix Scientifique Franco-Taiwanais and the Tsung-
in science parks. Application such as environmental monitoring and information network, intelligent transportation
ming Tu Award. All these efforts help develop practical partnerships with other countries while promoting diploma- system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipment management, monitoring and integration system,
intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficient transportation and traffic safety, thus creating a convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest- ment.
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera- personnel and the worldwide S&T community,
tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on public roofs and set up demonstration sites of MOST provides funding for domestic research
distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy-
teams to participate in international academic orga-
cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for
nizations. MOST also subsidizes scholars to attend
environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental
inteqrunaltitoyn.aSlucohnifnefroernmcaetsio,nhowldouinldtebrneaitniocnluadlesdeimni-thesmartparkdatabasetobeprocessedusingbigdataanalytics
for intelligence science park environmental management. nars, and invite foreign S&T experts for short visits
to Taiwan.
 ]]></page><page Index="29" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
Serving as the core for Taiwan's biomedical science research and industry development, the Hsinchu Biomedi- cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical Science and Product R&D Center, the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all under one umbrella. With focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides clinical trials, business seed planning, an innovative R&D network (R&D facilities and talent), clinical trial coopera- tion, and regulatory consulting services. Among the 58 approved companies in the Park, 24 specializes in R&D of new pharmaceuticals
MOST currently oversees 18 S&T divisions in 14 countries. In addition to promoting bilateral S&T cooperation, liaising with foreign S&T agencies, main- taining contacts with scholars residing abroad, and organizing overseas S&T seminars, these divisions have been actively recruiting overseas talents to meet the domestic needs for S&T development.
To further broaden and deepen cooperation for S&T innovation, MOST offers grants for overseas science and technology innovation centers to be established by domestic universities in collaboration with foreign agencies. Since 2017, 12 centers have been set up in 9 countries conducting research on humanities, medicine, nature, agriculture, and engineering.
Science and Technology Innovation Center for Taiwan- Philippines Indigenous Knowledge, Local Knowledge and Sustainable Studies
Overseas Divisions
12 Overseas Science &Technology Innovation Centers
Taiwan-Philippines Joint Water Quality Research and Innovation Center
Taiwan-Thailand Medical Technology, Science & Humanities Development Center
Vietnam-Taiwan Joint Plant Conservation Research Center
VAAS-NCHU Agricultural Science and Technology Innovation Cooperation
Center of Southeast Asian Ethnicities, Cultures and Societies
Taiwan-Malaysia Digital Technology International Centre
Taiwan and Sri Lanka Environmental Change Sciences and Technology Innovation Center
Taiwan-India Joint Research Center on Artificial Intelligence
Taiwan-Singapore Aging and Cancer Overseas Science and Technology Innovation Center
Taiwan-Malaysia Innovation Center for Clean Water and Sustainable Energy
Taiwan-Myanmar Overseas Economic Surveys Research Center
]]></page><page Index="30" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                                                                                                                                                                                                                               Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
Enhancement of Academia-Industry Relationship and Innovation
Academia-Industry-Research Collaboration
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, Amconaidtoersmainad-ienvdaluasttersySC&oT odpeverloaptmiveent RpelasnseaprocphosPedrobgy rdaifmferent government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
 Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
   Smart Science Parks
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
     Promotion of National Science & Technology Development
National Science & Technology Development Policies
Aiming to match the R&D seeds of the academia with the needs of private businesses, the Academia-Industry Cooperative Research Program, launched in 2008, encourages business- es to participate in university-based applied research projects, promotes collaboration on highly innovative research projects, sets rules for co-ownership of research results, and establishes alternative models for technology transfer authori- zation, thus increasing the effectiveness of indus- try-academia cooperation.
2019 685 joint projects approved
Since 2013, MOST and the Ministry of Eco-
nomic Affairs have been jointly funding the
2019
4projects of diverse disciplines approved
PIONEER Grants for Frontier Technologies Devel-
opment by Academia-Industry Cooperation
PIONEER Grants for AIC
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice
(PIONEER Grants for AIC) to encourage interna-
in science parks. Application such as environmental monitorinUgSa$n8d.i5nfmorimllioantiomnantcehtwinogrkin,vinetsetmlligeennt t transportation
tionally and regionally leading industries/business-
system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipmenatttmraacnteadgefrmomenitn,dmusotnryitoring and integration system,
es to form collaboration with the academia and
intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in
US$80million matching investment
conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster
engage in cooperative R&D on forward-looking industrial technologies that require long-term com-
generated since 2013
energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficient transportation and traffic safety, thus creating a
mitment. Such joint effort would enhance industrial
557patent applications made
convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest-
competitiveness and improve key patent portfolios
ment.
of Taiwan.
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera- tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on public roofs and set up demonstration sites of distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy- cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental quality. Such information would be included in the smart park database to be processed using big data analytics for intelligence science park environmental management.
US$21.3million grants given
1,945 doctoral and master students nurtured 699factories/firms involved US$8million R&D funds attracted
]]></page><page Index="31" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
S
c i
e
n
Promotion of National
Serving as the core for Taiwan's biomedical science research and industry development, the Hsinchu Biomedi-
Funded by MOST since 2013, Academia-In-
c
e
&
T
the academia to establish core technology labora-
e c
logy Development
h
n
cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical
dustry
Te
ch
n
olo
gica
lA
llian
ce P
roje
cts
e
nco
ura
ge
2019
Science and Product R&D Center, the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu
Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all
o
tories as a bridge to industry users. Providing a 2303factories/firms attracted to be National Science & Technology Development Policies
under one umbrella. With focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides
new platform for academia-industry collaboration, project participants
clinical trials, business seed planning, an innovative R&D network (R&D facilities and talent), clinical trial coopera-
these projects offer an innovative one-to-many
187new technologies and
tion, and regulatory consulting services. Among the 58 approved companies in the Park, 24 specializes in R&D of
model of cooperation, and are characterized by a
269innovative products jointly developed.
new pharmaceuticals
strict selection process, high rejection rate, and full-scale interaction between academic research- ers and their counterparts in industry. Research results and performance of such alliances are project indicators.
Academia-Industry Research (AIR) Center Scheme
Aiming to strengthen academia-industry relationship and establish long-term steady collab- oration, MOST offers a dollar-for-dollar matching investment grant to industries under the AIR Center Scheme. This grant lasting for 3-5 years with a ceiling of US$33 million per year serves to attract more topnotch industries, both domestic and foreign, to join hands with the government in developing internationally competitive technolo- gies and innovations as well as cultivating techni- cal talents. Fruits of R&D will be translated into industrial innovations for economic benefits.
Future
Attract US$6.7 worth of annual R&D
In a joint effort with the industrial sector to enhance competitiveness, MOST offers doctoral degree holders training/internship opportunities in
2019
782 PhDs enrolled for one-year
channel talents with research capabilities to the industry for R&D and to nurture high-level S&T talents through on-the-job training.
internship in 536collaborating corporations.
investment from industries
Cultivate over 300technical talents.
77% found jobs in industrial sector upon completion of training
Academia-Industry Technological Alliance Projects
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
Industrial Training / Internship Program for PhDs
]]></page><page Index="32" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                                                                                                                                                                                                                               Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
GLORIA Program
      Smart Science Parks
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
   To promote industrial application of academic R&D results, research institutes that possess
2019
Academia-Industry Mediators
Promotion of National
Science & Technology Development
abundant R&D capability and industrial experi- ence serve as the mediator between universities
Consultation provided for 256cases
49collaborations formed National Science & Technology Development Policies
and industries. These institutes take inventory of academic R&D results, screen and match cases with industries in need of such application, offering assistance for commercialization (technical value-added), patent portfolio analysis, utilization promotion and startup development.
US$4million revenue generated for universities/schools involved US$7.7 million startup investment attracted
The Global Research & Industry Alliance (GLO- RIA) program aims to accelerate the process of interlinking academic research achievements and domestic industrial development with the global trend and to establish an innovative collaborated ecosystem comprising universities, research tech- nology organizations (RTOs) and industries. Alliances are formed for the promotion of domestic R&D value and the competitiveness of cutting-edge technology innovation. Focus will be on developing advanced technologies, establish-
2019 354domestic/global enterprises joined
72 startups established
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice
ing industrial liaison centers, enhancing
4,267talents cultivated for industrial
in science parks. Application such as environmental monitoring and information network, intelligent transportation
academia-industry and international cooperation,
sector
connecting domestic R&D and industrial develop-
system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipment management, monitoring and integration system,
ment to the international trend, and ultimately
intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in
achieving sustainable alliance operation.
conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficient transportation and traffic safety, thus creating a convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest- ment.
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera- tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on public roofs and set up demonstration sites of distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy- cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental quality. Such information would be included in the smart park database to be processed using big data analytics for intelligence science park environmental management.
381talents nurtured
the alliance
US$6.5 million membership fee contributed
US$64.7million R&D investment brought in
]]></page><page Index="33" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Innovation and Entrepreneurship
Germination Program
Launched in 2011, the Germination Program helps
academic research institutes accelerate technological
diffusion by establishing mechanisms for the promotion
and application of R&D results. In 2018, germination
centers set up under the program were integrated with
Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
Promotion of National
Serving as the core for Taiwan's biomedical science research and industry development, the Hsinchu Biomedi- cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical
Science & Technology Development
Science and Product R&D Center, the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu
Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all
National Science & Technology Development Policies
66 new startups germinated under one umbrella. With focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides
US$50 million investment
tion, and regulatory consulting services. Among the 58 approved companies in the Park, 24 specializes in R&D of
clinical trials, business seed planning, an innovative R&D network (R&D facilities and talent), clinical trial coopera-
new pharmaceuticals
attracted
2019
2019 140overseas corporations joined
LEAP including nVIDIA, Taboola, Pfizer and Microsoft,
119 program fellows provided internships
33 program fellows sponsored to study at Stanford University, MIT, Massachusetts General Hospital, UC Berkeley and Duke University
the Global Research & Industry Alliance (GLORIA)
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national
program in exploring and developing forward-looking,
S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies,
original research with potential for commercial applica-
MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government
tions. The program also reviews and recommends prom-
depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
ising cases, helps grant recipients develop their business
model and technology (services), and systematically
facilitates high-potential research to evolve into new busi-
nesses or industries.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Aiming to create an ecosystem for innovations and expedite the commercialization of R&D results, the TRUST-U Project encourages academia-industry collab- oration to develop advanced and innovative technologies, produce key intellectual properties, and contribute to successful startups or mergers and acquisitions (M&As). As a national-level accelerator, the Taiwan Startup Insti- tute (TSI) is established to nurture high-valuation startups or M&As by fine-tuning and optimizing the business models of TRUST-U collaborations and defining their market position and product segmentation. As new busi- nesses prosper, more values will be created for the whole startup ecosystem and society will benefit.
2019 15startups established
US$54.3million investment US$125million worth startup
valuation
TRUST-U Project
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
(LEAP) Program to cultivate technical, innovative and entrepreneurial professionals while establishing an inno- vative platform that connects Taiwan to the world. Under the Program, doctorate-level talents with entrepreneurial aspirations are entitled to receive a living allowance of US$ 50,000 each and will be sent to Silicon Valley, France and Israel for a year of learning through coopera- tive projects with international corporations, startups, or reputable research institutions. This will cultivate high-level professionals for Taiwan and develop their entrepreneurial and strategic thinking abilities. By networking with the innovative startup community abroad, these professionals upon return can build links with over- seas innovative resources and contribute their expertise
LEAP Program
]]></page><page Index="34" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                                                                                                                                                                                                                               Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
From Intellectual Property to Initial Public Offering
   MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
Taiwan Tech Arena (TTA)
     Smart Science Parks
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
   Incubation of Startups Promotion of National
Science & Technology Development
Launched in 2011, the Germination Program
helps academic research institutes accelerate 2019 technological diffusion by establishing mecha-
National Science & Technology D14ecvalles floor appmlicaetionstoPrgaonilziecd ies
nisms for the promotion and application of R&D results. In 2018, germination centers set up under the program were integrated with the Global Research & Industry Alliance (GLORIA) program in exploring and developing forward-looking, origi- nal research with potential for commercial applica- tions. The program also reviews and recommends promising cases, helps grant recipients develop their business model and technology (services), and systematically facilitates high-potential research to evolve into new businesses or indus- tries.
190startups helped get off the ground US$102 million investment funds raised 651job opportunities created
Launched in 2018, TTA serves as a co-creation platform for startups, accelerators, venture capital and corporate partners to connect global resourc-
Since 2018
es, build a high-tech startup-friendly ecosystem,
International technology startup-relat- ed organizations from countries includ-
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance s e
e
q
li
s are put to practice
anidnfsocsietenrcheigpahr-ktesc.hApepnlitcreatpiorennseuucrhshasipe.nItvisrotnhmeefinrstatlmonitorin g
a
nd
f orm
a nsportation
system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipmen
domestic and Asian international Tech-Focus hub
intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial waste
,
L
a
b
s,
IA
P
,
B
E
attracting global and domestic talents and actively conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT
,
c
t
ed
fostering innovation of hi-tech industries.
energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficie
a
c
d
o
re
m
es
ti
c
d
Delegations have been sent to large-scale
u
p
s
convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environm
h
ment. in cultivating new tech startups and
exhibitions including Consumer Electronics Show
r
e
d
h
r
e
n
i
es
(CES) in the US, VivaTech in France, Innovfest
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, sc ie
n
Untboorsu,nbdutinalsSoinpgraopmorte, tMheedinTsetacllhationnBoofsstolnarapnhdotovoltaics
o n
p
distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Wa
TechCrunch. Attention from overseas venture
cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply
,
capitals and international companies has been
.
n
u
e
P
r
k
m
r
i
se
d
4
4
environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are a attracted and billions of global business opportuni-
tw a
s ng
n
d for intelligence science park environmental management.
e
quality. Such information would be included in the smart park ties have been won.
a
2 2
0
1
9
i
p
e
i
a
r
t
u
p
e
s
t
i
v
a
l
0
1
t t
a a
9
M M
T T
i
p
e
t t
r
t
i
n
g
F
ra
n
c
e
a
n
d
C
a
n
a
d
a
l
D
o
t
i
c
a
n
d
ig
n
a
c
c
e
le
r
a
to
r
s
t
m
i
n
cl
u
d
in
g
M
O
X
S
p
a
r
k
n
g
a nd
S
A
cc
e
le
ra
to
r
a
n
d
T
e
ch
s
ta
r
s
a
ttra
r
C
o
he
m
th
a
n
2
0
0
d
o
a
n
s can foster
,
.
fo
r
e
i
g
n
s
ta
r
t
tio
e
P
a
r
t
ne
w
it
m
o
t
h
a
n
2
0
c
om
p
a
tr
a
s
si
s
tin
g
t
h
e
ir
e
x
p
a
n
si
o
n
in
t
h
e
i
n
t
e
e
ergy opera-
t
io
na
bl
r
o
te
re
A
t
C
S
2
0
1
h
e
ld
a
s
g
as
u
T
T
A
d
e
le
g
a
tio
a
tE
r
ka
a
c
o
p
c a
te
c
h
ta
rt
p
s
f
ic
h
ig
i
n
In
o
v
a
ti
o
n
A
w
.
e e
r
u
w
n
n t
w it
ls
r
c
A
n
ta b
a
rd
s
e e
vic
n
a
t
t
m
es
fo
r
e
or
l
a
a
n
c
o
s
u
r
a
n
em
m
ion system, t
te
m
d
c
e
p ar
k s
n
E
9
a
t
L
V
e
o
r
f
a
r
a
n
u
ic
o
l
m
a
rk
e
t
.
i
a
k, in
t gra
n
ion n
e
g
en
t,
o
ns
la
to m
in
p
rn
s
u
,
o
w
h
e
h
t
w
o
t
h
e
a
pr
cessed using big data analytics o
p
i
S S
a
u
p
F F
s
t
a
a
lou
s tr
on
g
c o
t
m
ta
ll e
d
f
pr
o
s
e
t
o
a
a tic
w
r
ty
s
d
c
t
t io
o
b
a
e
a
,
a
t
tr
a
c
te
d
t
e
g
e
o t
n
p
a
st
w
re a
o
r
o
vironmental
m
om
m
e
i
v
a
l
la
n
a
p
m
e
at
e r
t
t
r
t
ic
u
n
e t
n
p
ts
a
e
i
in
t
s
t
e
it
m
pp
w
t
to
r
tin g
r
a
i
y
s
implemented in
iv e
n
a
te
t
io
m
a
e
es s
for
a t
a
cting invest-
e
lig
n
tr
h
n and traffic safety, thus creating a
T
e se
fa
n
fs and set up demonstration sites of
o
ly
b
re n
r
in
g
e
ls
s
o
e
m
w a
e
t
u
n t
is
rried out for
c
b
ili
l
e
n
p
o
r water recy-
n
e
ti e
rn
a
-
]]></page><page Index="35" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
Promotion of National
Serving as the core for Taiwan's biomedical science research and industry development, the Hsinchu Biomedi- cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical
Science & Technology Development
Science aTndo hPerolpdudcotmRe&sDticCsetnatretur,ptshebuHilsdininchteurnBaiotimoneadlical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu
Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all
National Science & Technology Development Policies
connections, the TIEC offers subsidies under
122startups sent to the US
under one umbrella. With focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides
the TTA Silicon Valley Grant Program to start-
clinical trials, business seed planning, an innovative R&D network (R&D facilities and talent), clinical trial coopera-
36meetup events organized in SV
tion, and regulatory consulting services. Among the 58 approved companies in the Park, 24 specializes in R&D of
ups with high market potential to expand their
21key accelerators and venture capitalists connected
businesses – a beachhead strategy for new pharmaceuticals
domestic startups. In addition to providing soft-landing services, mentoring, and co-work- ing space, TTA SV also assist in partnering with local accelerators and corporate giants as well as investor matching via the Angel-Ven- ture Capital network for crowdfunding.
8international investment matching events organized in Taiwan
Launched in 2013, the Applied Research Incubation Projects match academic research with industrial needs and nurture high-tech innovative businesses. The projects offer grants for pioneering product-oriented research with application potential. The mile- stone-based funding and portfolio manage- ment mechanisms help incubate research teams and improve market application of R&D results. Greater emphasis has been given to research on pharmaceuticals and medical devices.
2019 320potential cases screened
74startups assisted US$14million funding raised.
2019
> 100 cases given in-depth assessment 38academic teams
R&D results commercialized: -smart medicine devices
-leukocyte reduction filter
-in vitro diagnostic reagents for cancer -mobile application for coronary heart
disease detection
21biomedical startups established US$36.7million cumulative paid-up capital
7 startups in biotechnology and pharmaceutical research established at science parks.
Taiwan Innovation and Entrepreneurship Center (TIEC)
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Applied Research Incubation Projects
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
]]></page><page Index="36" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Green Energy Technology
Promotion of National
Joint Research & Development Program
Science & Technology Development
In line with the government promotion of green
energy industry, the Green Energy Technology
2019
National Science & Technology Development Policies
Joint Research and Development Program plays
53research teams formed among 87 companies
an important role in the national energy transition policy. Strategic R&D focuses on “frontier materi- als”, “energy conservation”, “sustainable technolo- gy” and “smart system”, emphasizing also allying key industries with frontier technology to facilitate application of R&D results. The Program aims to promote development of innovative green energy technology and support integration of potential green technology innovations.
589green energy-related research talents cultivated.
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice in science parks. Application such as environmental monitoring and information network, intelligent transportation system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipment management, monitoring and integration system, intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficient transportation and traffic safety, thus creating a convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest- ment.
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera- tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on public roofs and set up demonstration sites of distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy- cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental quality. Such information would be included in the smart park database to be processed using big data analytics for intelligence science park environmental management.
353 journal articles published 36patents obtained
12technology transfers facilitated US$4 million raised from private sector.
Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
Smart Science Parks
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
]]></page><page Index="37" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
Promotion of National
Artificial Intelligence Innovation Ecosystem
Serving as the core for Taiwan's biomedical science research and industry development, the Hsinchu Biomedi- cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical
Science & Technology Development
Science and Product R&D Center, the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu
Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all
National Science & Technology Development Policies
under one umbrella. With focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides clinical trials, business seed planning, an innovative R&D network (R&D facilities and talent), clinical trial coopera- tion, and regulatory consulting services. Among the 58 approved companies in the Park, 24 specializes in R&D of new pharmaceuticals
R&D Service - AI Cloud Service Platform Build national AI cloud infrastructure for R&D
MOST formulates gDueidvelolipnesesrvaicnesdapndotleicihensoloagsieswoeflAl Iassyspteumtsfofor arwdvanrdcedthsemavritsaipopnlicatniodnstrategies for national
S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies,
Provide a common and sharable AI and Big Data Computing Platform across academia and industries
MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government
depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Facilitate AI innovation and interdisciplinary technology integration
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Value-added Innovation - AI Research Center Create environment for AI innovation and devlopment of cutting-edge technology Nurture AI start-up companies
Establish International AI innovation research centers
Cultivate AI talents
Creativity & Practice - Robot Makerspace Bring makers to realize their dreams
Build people-oriented international flagship makerspace of serving robots Establish open innovation platform at scientific research level
Attract schools, industries and international startups for robot testing
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
Industrial Pilot Program - AI Chip Moonshot Program Promote R&D on semiconductor manufacturing and SoC design for AI edge
Provide core technologies of AI industry
Cultivate talents for cross-field semiconductor SoC design
Strengthen international competitiveness of semiconductor industry
Social Participation - Formosa Grand Challenge Accelerate development of core phonetic technology
Foster R&D on voice application in human-machine communication
Promote advances in core technologies for speech recognition and semantic analysis Build big data bank for multi-situational conversation to enhance AI technology
]]></page><page Index="38" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Hsinchu Science Park
Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
Promotion of National Science & Technology Development
National Science & Technology Development Policies
parks combine R&D, production, working, living, and recreational facilities into lifestyle-oriented communi- ties. As magnets for S&T talents and enterprises, the science parks are high-tech bases that balance regional development and promote overall industrial upgrade. They have different but complementary focuses of industrial development. Together, they form a high-tech industrial innovation corridor. Their success over the past four decades not only brought economic prosperity, but also made a name for
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice in science parks. Application such as environmental monitoring and information network, intelligent transportation system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipment management, monitoring and integration system, intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficient transportation and traffic safety, thus creating a convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest- ment.
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera- tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on public roofs and set up demonstration sites of distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy- cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental quality. Such information would be included in the smart park database to be processed using big data analytics for intelligence science park environmental management.
Development of Science Parks
Features & Locations
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
Smart Science Parks
Central Taiwan Science Park
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
Southern Taiwan Science Park
]]></page><page Index="39" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
Promotion of National
Serving as the core for Taiwan's biomedical science research and industry development, the Hsinchu Biomedi- cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical
Science & Technology Development
Science and Product R&D Center, the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu
Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all
National Science & Technology Development Policies
under one umbrella. With focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides clinical trials, business seed planning, an innovative R&D network (R&D facilities and talent), clinical trial coopera- tion, and regulatory consulting services. Among the 58 approved companies in the Park, 24 specializes in R&D of new pharmaceuticals
Longtan Park 107
HsinchMuOBSioTmfoermdiuclatleSscgiueidnecleinePsaarknd3p8olicies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national
S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies,
MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government
Hsinchu Park 685
depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Hsinchu Science Park 1,375
Advanced Research Park 36
Central Taiwan Science Park 1,485
Jhunan Park 123
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Tongluo Park 350 Houli Park 256
Taichung Park 466 Erlin Park 631
Huwei Park 96 Tainan Park1,043
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
Kaohsiung Park 567
Yilan Park 71
Southern Taiwan Science Park 1,610
]]></page><page Index="40" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
Promotion of National Science & Technology Development
National Science & Technology Development Policies
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice in science parks. Application such as environmental monitoring and information network, intelligent transportation system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipment management, monitoring and integration system, intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficient transportation and traffic safety, thus creating a convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest- ment.
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera- tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on public roofs and set up demonstration sites of distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy- cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental quality. Such information would be included in the smart park database to be processed using big data analytics for intelligence science park environmental management.
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies,
MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences. FOR NEXT DECADE
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
Status of Development
Hsinchu Science Park
● Enhance ICT industry value chain competitiveness through software/hardware integration
Smart Science Parks
● Foster biomedical clusters through developing high-end medical devices, new pharmaceuticals, and medical specialties Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
● Implement park renewal and create a friendly sustainable environment for the on-campus companies and staff as well as neighboring residents
Central Taiwan Science Park
● Develop intelligent automatic system integration system and smart medical assistive technology
● Attract low-carbon, light and energy-saving industries ●
Southern Taiwan Science Park
● Promote “Be a Maker” by establishing an AI robot makerspace ● Develop medical device cluster and healthcare industry
● ntegrate and upgrade semiconductor industry chain
● Establish precision machinery and aerospace clusters
FOCUS OF
DEVELOPMENT
]]></page><page Index="41" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
Promotion of National
Serving as the core for Taiwan's biomedical science research and industry development, the Hsinchu Biomedi- cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical
Science & Technology Development
Science and Product R&D Center, the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu
Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all
National Science & Technology Development Policies
under one umbrella. With focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides clinical trials, business seed planning, an innovative R&D network (R&D facilities and talent), clinical trial coopera- tion, and regulatory consulting services. Among the 58 approved companies in the Park, 24 specializes in R&D of new pharmaceuticals
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
]]></page><page Index="42" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
Promotion of National Science & Technology Development
National Science & Technology Development Policies
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice in science parks. Application such as environmental monitoring and information network, intelligent transportation system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipment management, monitoring and integration system, intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficient transportation and traffic safety, thus creating a convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest- ment.
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera- tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on public roofs and set up demonstration sites of distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy- cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental quality. Such information would be included in the smart park database to be processed using big data analytics for intelligence science park environmental management.
Smart Science Parks
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
]]></page><page Index="43" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
Promotion of National
Serving as the core for Taiwan's biomedical science research and industry development, the Hsinchu Biomedi- cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical
Science & Technology Development
Science and Product R&D Center, the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu
Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all
National Science & Technology Development Policies
under one umbrella. With focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides clinical trials, business seed planning, an innovative R&D network (R&D facilities and talent), clinical trial coopera- tion, and regulatory consulting services. Among the 58 approved companies in the Park, 24 specializes in R&D of new pharmaceuticals
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
]]></page><page Index="44" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Foundations and Administrative Institution
Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
Promotion of National Science & Technology Development
National Science & Technology Development Policies
Established in 2003, the National Applied Research Laboratories (NARLabs) is an integrat- ed research conglomerate with a vision of pursu- ing global excellence and creating local impact. As the premier interdisciplinary research institution, NARLabs is dedicated to creating cutting-edge
socio-economic development, and serves as the bridge and integrator of application-based research efforts to achieving the national S&T policy objectives.
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice in science parks. Application such as environmental monitoring and information network, intelligent transportation system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipment management, monitoring and integration system, intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficient transportation and traffic safety, thus creating a convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest- ment.
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera- tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on public roofs and set up demonstration sites of distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy- cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental quality. Such information would be included in the smart park database to be processed using big data analytics for intelligence science park environmental management.
National Applied Research Laboratories (NARLabs)
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
8 national laboratories
National Laboratory Animal Center (NLAC)
National Center for Research on Earthquake Engineering (NCREE)
National Space Organization (NSPO)
National Center for High-performance Computing (NCHC)
Taiwan Semiconductor Research Institute (TSRI)
Taiwan Instrument Research Institute (TIRI)
ScieAncnen&uTeaclhnAolgogeynPcoliycyBReusedagrceh tanadnIndformSa&tioTn CDenetevrelopment Fund, 2015-2019 Smart Science Parks
(STPI)
Taiwan Ocean Research Institute (TORI)
]]></page><page Index="45" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
Promotion of National
Serving as the core for Taiwan's biomedical science research and industry development, the Hsinchu Biomedi- cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical
Science & Technology Development
Science and Product R&D Center, the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu
Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all
National Science & Technology Development Policies
under one umbrella. With focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides clinical trials, business seed planning, an innovative R&D network (R&D facilities and talent), clinical trial coopera- tion, and regulatory consulting services. Among the 58 approved companies in the Park, 24 specializes in R&D of new pharmaceuticals
Earth Science and Environment
Satellite systems engineering
Spacecraft bus development Electro-optical remote sensing instrument Satellite control and operation
National Space Organization (NSPO)
Engineering (NCREE)
Information Center (STPI)
Remote sensing image processing
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national
S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies,
MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government
depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
National Center for Research on Earthquake
Operation and service of research vessels and exploratory equipment
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Seismic testing and numerical simulation
technologies
                                                
technologies
Earthquake loss estimation technologies
Taiwan Ocean Research Institute (TORI)
Marine environmental long-term observation and modeling
Marine exploration technology and facility R&D
Ocean information database establishment and value-added service
Science and Technology Policy Research
Science & Technology Policy Research and
))
))
S&T issue studies
))Patent mapping and information analysis ))Innovation ecosystem research ))Government S&T program management
Integration S&T information services
Innovation and entrepreneurship talent development
))
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
  
]]></page><page Index="46" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                                                                                                                                                                                                                               Biomedical Technology
Electronic Information and
Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
National Laboratory Animal Center (NLAC)
))                              
))Management of reproduction and breeding of ))laboratory animals
))                                                ))Sterile mouse and isolation technology
Communication
National Center for High-performance Computing (NCHC)
))High-performance computing ))Big data computing
))AI computing cloud services ))Network and information security
High-end medical material implant surgery and
)) MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national
               
S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies,
MOFaScTilirtyevmieawnsa,gemmoennittoprsrofaensdsioenvallucaoteusnsSel&linTg development plans proposed by different government ))Chip design tape-out procedure integration
depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
))Pioneering device and processing technology
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
tio
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
Taiwan Semiconductor Research Institute (TSRI)
 Annual Agency Budget Alloc
))Heterogeneous chip integration technology
a
t
i
t
o
e
ri
de
n
,
2
0
te
c
2
0n and analysis technology Taiwan Instrument Research Institute (TIRI)
al
))Chip packaging and measuring technology
))M
a
))Opto-electro-mechanical system integration ))Precision opto-mechanical technology ))Electro-optics remote sensing
))                                      
technology
  Smart Science Parks
    &&
   Promotion of National Science & Technology Development
National Science & Technology Development Policies
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice in science parks. Application such as environmental monitoring and information network, intelligent transportation system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipment management, monitoring and integration system, intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficient transportation and traffic safety, thus creating a convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest- ment.
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera- tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on public roofs and set up demonstration sites of distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy- cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental quality. Such information would be included in the smart park database to be processed using big data analytics for intelligence science park environmental management.
]]></page><page Index="47" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
Promotion of National
Serving as the core for Taiwan's biomedical science research and industry development, the Hsinchu Biomedi- cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical
Science & Technology Development
Science and Product R&D Center, the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu
Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all
National Science & Technology Development Policies
under one umbrella. With focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides clinical trials, business seed planning, an innovative R&D network (R&D facilities and talent), clinical trial coopera- tion, and regulatory consulting services. Among the 58 approved companies in the Park, 24 specializes in R&D of new pharmaceuticals
Located in Hsinchu Science Park, the National Synchrotron Radiation Research Center (NSRRC) operates a high-performance synchrotron, provid- ing X-rays of great brightness unattainable in conventional laboratories. The synchrotron light source is an indispenably sharp tool for exploring the world invisible to the naked eyes and cutting-edge research in basic science. Users from academic and technological communities worldwide take advantage of the facilities at NSRRC to explore the vast universe, scrutinize the complicated structures of life, discover novel nanomaterials, create sustainable green energy, and unveil living things in the distant past.
ANSTO facility, which offer domestic and foreign researchers another powerful research tool. These worldclass research facilities offer the state-of-the-art instruments and innovative tech- niques to explore frontier science and applied research, to cultivate high-tech talents, and promote international cooperation.
There are two synchrotron radiation facilities at NSRRC: Taiwan Light Source (TLS) and Taiwan Photon Source (TPS). In addition, Taiwan has also constructed two dedicated beamlines at Japan's SPring-8 synchrotron radiation facility (8 GeV), and is responsible for operation and maintenance of the SIKA (Spin-polarized Inelastic K-space Analyzer) neutron instrument at Australia's
With high spatial resolution, high time resolution, and coherent light source, TPS is one of the brightest synchrotron light sources in the world. To maximize its benefits, the NSRRC has made plans to construct 25 beamlines in three phases. The 7 beamlines of Phase I have been constructed, the 9 beamlines of Phase II are currently under construction, and the Phase III construction will commence in the near future. With an accelerator and beamlines par excellence, TPS will blaze a trail to science frontiers
NSRRC possesses one of the most advanced synchrotron facilities in the world and its pioneering capabilities keep Taiwan at the forefront of scientif- ic research.
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Aerial view of the National Synchrotron Radiation Research Center
National Synchrotron Radiation Research Center
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
]]></page><page Index="48" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                                                                                                                                                                                                                                Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
National Science & Technology Center for Disaster Reduction
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
      Smart Science Parks
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
    Promotion of National Science & Technology Development
National Science & Technology Development Policies
MOST has effectively integrated cross-disciplinary scien- tific research achievements and resources on disaster risk reduction through the National Science and Technology Center for Disaster Reduction (NCDR), and incorporated them into policies and practices. Local research institutions in 22 cities and counties have participated in programs designed to enhance information exchanges among central and local governments for both disaster risk reduction and emergency preparedness. Prompt dissemination of real-time local disaster information and comprehensive early warning disaster alerts contribute to mitigate disaster risk and impact on human life and property.
In 2018, the NCDR cooperated with LINE Taiwan to launch the NCDR official account featuring user-friendly interactive functions of LINE mobile instant messaging application. Practi- cal information related to meteorology, hydrology, transporta- tion, and livelihood can be automatically broadcast to subscrib- ers with catchy illustrations. Alerts related to rainfall, wind force, temperature, reservoir water level, air quality, ultraviolet radiation, and lightning, are also integrated into NCDR LINE channel for quick access to subscribers. As of March 2020, subscriptions of this application has exceeded 1.11 million.
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice in science parks. Application such as environmental monitoring and information network, intelligent transportation system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipment management, monitoring and integration system, intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficient transportation and traffic safety, thus creating a convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest- ment.
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera- tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on public roofs and set up demonstration sites of distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy- cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental quality. Such information would be included in the smart park database to be processed using big data analytics for intelligence science park environmental management.
]]></page><page Index="49" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[ Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park
new pharmaceuticals
Promotion of National
Serving as the core for Taiwan's biomedical science research and industry development, the Hsinchu Biomedi- cal Science Park is a knowledge-, innovation- and incubation-oriented science park, featuring the Biomedical
Science & Technology Development
Science and Product R&D Center, the Hsinchu Biomedical Science Park Incubation Center, and the Hsinchu
Biomedical Science Park Hospital. These facilities bring treatment, research, industrial and lifestyle needs all
National Science & Technology Development Policies
under one umbrella. With focus on clusters and adopting the Si2C one-stop shop concept, the Park provides clinical trials, business seed planning, an innovative R&D network (R&D facilities and talent), clinical trial coopera- tion, and regulatory consulting services. Among the 58 approved companies in the Park, 24 specializes in R&D of
Promote and conduct activities related to applied research and development on disaster management
Conduct mission-oriented research activities for enhancing capacity and capability related to issues of natural disaster Seek collaborations with domestic and international institutes
Facilitate scientific knowledge and technological advantages for practical implementations to benefit the whole society
Facilitate consultations and policy advices proposed by the Disaster Prevention and Protection Expert Consultation Committee
Apply outputs of science and technology to disaster risk reduction and emergency preparedness
Join operations at the Central Emergency Operation Center by offering integrated information and timely suggestions Deliver common operational pictures to central and local governments through the decision support system
Build up international partnerships to exchange experiences and conduct joint projects
Serve as the contact window of MOST at the Central Emergency Operation Center
Help to disseminate disaster alerts produced by government agencies and private sectors through multiple information channels
Collaborate with domestic research
contributions for reducing disaster risk and enhancing emergency preparedness
Conduct on-site investigations and integrate inter-disciplinary collaborations for proposing holistic assessments and advices
Update annually update hazard maps for raising government and public awareness
Provide relevant services related to disaster management
Monitor processes of long-term post-disaster recovery by field surveys
Mandates of NCDR
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national
S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies,
Daily Operation government MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different
depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Operations During Emergency
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
Post-Disaster Actions
]]></page><page Index="50" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                   Publications
https://reurl.cc/MvWykK (English version) https://reurl.cc/GVgK6v (English version) https://pse.is/RWB49
https://jbiomedsci.biomedcentral.com/
https://www.springer.com/journal/10763
https://read.dukeupress.edu/easts
http://ap0922.most.gov.tw/sd/
Directory
Ministry of Science and Technology
No. 106, Sec. 2, Heping E. Rd., Da-an Dist., Taipei City 10622
Tel: +886-2-2737-7992 https://www.most.gov.tw/
Hsinchu Science Park Bureau
No. 2, Hsin-Ann Rd., Hsinchu Science Park, Hsinchu City 30016
Tel: +886-3-577-3311
Fax: +886-3-577-6222 https://www.sipa.gov.tw/
Central Taiwan Science Park Bureau
No. 2, Jhongke Rd., Situn Dist., Taichung City 40763 Tel: +886-4-2565-8588
Fax: +886-4-2565-8288
https://www.ctsp.gov.tw/
Southern Taiwan Science Park Bureau
No. 22, Nanke 3rd Rd., Xinshi Dist., Tainan City 74147 Tel: +886-6-505-1001
Fax: +886-6-505-0470
https://www.stsp.gov.tw/
National Applied Research Laboratories
3F., No. 106, Sec. 2, Heping E. Rd., Da-an Dist., Taipei City 10622
Tel: +886-2-2737-8000
Fax: +886-2-2737-8044 https://www.narlabs.org.tw/
National Synchrotron Radiation Research Center
No. 101, Hsin-Ann Rd., Hsinchu Science Park, Hsinchu City 30076
Tel: +886-3-578-0281
Fax: +886-3-578-9816 https://www.nsrrc.org.tw/
National Science and Technology Center for Disaster Reduction
9F., No. 200, Sec. 3, Beixin Rd., Xindian Dist.,
New Taipei City 23143
Tel: +886-2-8195-8600
Fax: +886-2-8912-7766 https://www.ncdr.nat.gov.tw/
          Ministry of Science and Technology Review
National Science and Technology Development Plan (2017-2020)
Indicators of Science and Technology, Taiwan
Journal of Biomedical Science
International Journal of Science and Mathematics Education
East Asian Science, Technology and Society: An International Journal
Science Development (in Chinese)
]]></page><page Index="51" isMAC="false"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="52" isMAC="true"><![CDATA[                                                                                                                                                                                                            Science Park Revenue, 2015-2019
MOST formulates guidelines and policies as well as puts forward the vision and strategies for national S&T development. To ensure integrated and consistent implementation of development policies, MOST reviews, monitors and evaluates S&T development plans proposed by different government depart-ments, appraises budget, and organizes national S&T conferences.
Annual Agency Budget Allocation, 2020
Science Park Employees, 2015-2019
Smart Science Parks
Annual Agency Budget and S&T Development Fund, 2015-2019
    Promotion of National Science & Technology Development
National Science & Technology Development Policies
To promote innovative transformation and to enhance service quality, smart applications are put to practice in science parks. Application such as environmental monitoring and information network, intelligent transportation system, 3D geographic coordinate system, public equipment management, monitoring and integration system, intelligent disaster prevention system, and industrial wastewater management system are implemented in conjunction with trendy technologies including Big Data, IoT, and cloud computing. These facilities can foster energy and water saving, carbon and waste reduction, efficient transportation and traffic safety, thus creating a convenient living space and an ideal entrepreneurial environment with strong competitiveness for attracting invest- ment.
To establish a low-carbon green-energy environment, science parks not only bring renewable energy opera- tors, but also promote the installation of solar photovoltaics on public roofs and set up demonstration sites of distributed power systems (with energy storage systems). Water reclamation plants are also set up for water recy- cle so as to diversify water sources and ensure stable supply. Automatic wastewater treatment is carried out for environmental protection. Air-quality monitoring systems are also installed for prompt warnings on environmental quality. Such information would be included in the smart park database to be processed using big data analytics for intelligence science park environmental management.
]]></page></pages></Search>